

# SONNY M. DAY

WORDPRESS WEB DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Goal-oriented WordPress web developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving.

Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer service.

#### SKILLS

Coding Languages, CMS, Themes, Plugins and Tools HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, DOM Manipulation, PHP, WooCommerce, Twitter Bootstrap, Skeleton Framework, HTML5 Boilerplate, Elementor, WP Bakery, Oxygen Builder, Divi, Avada, Astra, Jupiter, PSD to WordPress, Brilliant Directories, Revolution Slider, Custom Post types, CPanel, Photoshop, Canva

## CHARACTER REFERENCES

#### Jim Louis

Owner/CEO
Net Prophets Inc.
jim@bestplumbers.com

#### **Renae Christine**

Owner/CEO
Cupcake Training
renae@cupcaketrainings.com

## HOW TO REACH ME

Cell: +63948-046-7188

Email: sonnym.day25@gmail.com

Address: Block 3 Lot 1 Phase 2 San Lorenzo Village, Bago Gallera, Davao City

Philippines

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/sonny-day-3110b098

#### CAREER SUMMARY

#### **WordPress Website Developer**

Net Prophets Inc. | Dec 2014 - Sep 2021

- Design and create WordPress websites for clients using the latest technologies.
- Code and edit WordPress template files.
- Use the latest technologies in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and JQuery to customize WordPress themes.
- Create beautiful web pages using Elementor, Oxygen Builder, WP Bakery, Beaver Builder, Divi, Asta, Avada, Jupiter and more.
- Migrate or fix hacked websites.

#### **WorPress Developer**

Battlestar Digital | Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

- Created WordPress websites for clients
- Clone or create a pixel-perfect copy of an existing website
- · migrated websites to other hosting

### WordPress / Woocommerce Technical Support Specialist

Cupcake Trainings | Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

- Provided technical assistance to clients about their WooCommerce websites
- Gave suggestions on how to SEO optimize sites

#### **Wordpress Developer**

Creative Indie | Apr 2014 - Apr 2016

- Built WordPress websites for clients
- Customized themes, created logos and graphics
- Rebuilt hacked or malware-infected websites

## **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

University of Southeastern Philippines Bachelor of Arts in English | 2002-2006